<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><!DOCTYPE task PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DITA Task//EN" "task.dtd"[]>
<task xml:lang="en-us" id="A2A4568E-43CA114-8A55A795926C979-0D6A5D">
  <title>Extrude Faces</title>
  <shortdesc>You can extrude one or more faces of 3D solids at the
 specified height and path.</shortdesc>
  <taskbody>
    <context>
      <p>Negative value
 extrudes faces along to the positive normal; positive value extrudes faces
 along to the negative normal. After
 specifying the height, the system prompts you to specify the angle of taper for extrusion. If you specify the angular
 value is greater than 0, the plane tapers in from the base object; if the value is negative, the face tapers out. By default, the value is of 0, which extrudes
 the face</p>
      <p>perpendicular. The extrusion stops
 when the tapered face shrinks to a point.</p>
      <p>If you select Path option, the selected face extrudes at the specified line or curve objects. The objects that can
 be specified as an extrusion path contains line, circle, arc, ellipse, ellipse
 arc, polyline, and spline. These objects
 should not be coplanar with the object,
 nor should have areas of high curvature. Genera ly, one of the endpoints of the selected
 extrusion path should lie in the center of the face to extrude, if not, the systemwill do it.</p>
      <p>
        <table>
          <tgroup cols="1" colsep="1" rowsep="1">
            <colspec colname="c1" align="left" />
            <tbody>
              <row>
                <entry colname="c1">
                  <fig>
                    <image href="../graphics/ZWCAD_UG_manual_2020_topic414_image001.png" />
                  </fig>
                </entry>
              </row>
            </tbody>
          </tgroup>
        </table>
 To extrude
 a solid face</p>
    </context>
    <steps>
      <step>
        <cmd>Choose Modify &gt; Solids Editing &gt; Extrude Faces from the main menu.</cmd>
      </step>
      <step>
        <cmd>Select the face(s) to extrude, andpress
 Enter.</cmd>
      </step>
      <step>
        <cmd>Do one of the following:</cmd>
      </step>
      <step>
        <cmd>Specify the height of extrusion.</cmd>
      </step>
      <step>
        <cmd>Type P and press Enter to select a path for extrusion.</cmd>
      </step>
      <step>
        <info>
          <table>
            <tgroup cols="1" colsep="1" rowsep="1">
              <colspec colname="c1" align="left" />
              <tbody>
                <row>
                  <entry colname="c1">
                    <image href="../graphics/ZWCAD_UG_manual_2020_topic414_image002.png" />
                  </entry>
                </row>
              </tbody>
            </tgroup>
          </table>
 If you specified a height, specify
 a taper angle.</info>
      </step>
    </steps>
    <result>
      <p>Left: Select the entity to extrude, and then specify
 the face(s) to extrude (A), and the height of extrusion or path Right:
 The resulting entity
 with the face extruded to position (B)</p>
    </result>
  </taskbody>
</task>