<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><!DOCTYPE task PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DITA Task//EN" "task.dtd"[]>
<task xml:lang="en-us" id="A72A6365-C4A1879-35A7E5392FECE2B-05D32D">
  <title>Choose Transmittal Options</title>
  <shortdesc>You can specify the following
 transmittal setups when creating transmittal package, which greatly
 facilitates using the
 etransmit function.</shortdesc>
  <taskbody>
    <context>
      <ul>
        <li>Specify transmittal package type to be created as ZIP file, self-extracting EXE file, and folder (a specified folder
 position where the drawing will be packaged
 or copied)</li>
        <li>Choose options among Use
 organized folder structure, Place all files in
 one folder, Keep files and folders
 as is, to organize folder
 structure of transmitted files in a logicalstructure.</li>
        <li>Add password protection for transmittal package
 of the ZIP file and self-extracted EXE.</li>
        <li>Select Include fonts option to
 get all the font files associative to transmittal package (TTF and SHX), which facilitate receiver to view
 the drawing file.</li>
        <li>Send the transmittal package
 and transmittal report in form of an e-mail attachment to relevant users.</li>
      </ul>
      <p>It should be noticed
 that, regardless of file
 structure included in the
 created transmittal package,
 absolute path of dependent
 files that are relative to the drawing file will be converted to a relative
 path or not include path,
 so that you can easily
 find themwhile opening
 or editing drawing
 files.</p>
      <p>
        <table>
          <tgroup cols="1" colsep="1" rowsep="1">
            <colspec colname="c1" align="left" />
            <tbody>
              <row>
                <entry colname="c1">
                  <fig>
                    <image href="../graphics/ZWCAD_UG_manual_2020_topic776_image001.png" />
                  </fig>
                </entry>
              </row>
            </tbody>
          </tgroup>
        </table>
 To create transmittal package in the specified
 folder</p>
    </context>
    <steps>
      <step>
        <cmd>Select File &gt; etransmit from the
 mainmenu.</cmd>
      </step>
      <step>
        <cmd>In the Create
 Transmittal dialog box, under Files Tree or Files Table area, click Add File button.</cmd>
      </step>
      <step>
        <cmd>In the Open folder,
 select the file to be added to the transmittal package, and then</cmd>
        <info>
          <p>click Open. The user can optionally repeat this procedure
 to add more files into transmittalpackage.</p>
        </info>
      </step>
      <step>
        <cmd>To clear the
 selection of files being added into the transmittal package,
 click the check box marks beside any files on the Files Tree or Files Table.</cmd>
      </step>
      <step>
        <cmd>Clickthe Transmittal Setups button, select
 a transmittal setup
 from the Transmittal Setups dialog box, and then click Modify
 button.</cmd>
      </step>
      <step>
        <cmd>In the Modify Transmittal Setup dialog box, set the transmittal package type as Folder (set of files).</cmd>
      </step>
      <step>
        <cmd>Under Transmittal File Folder,
 click Browse to specify the folder where the transmittalpackage to be created.
 A standard file selection dialog box is displayed.</cmd>
      </step>
      <step>
        <cmd>Select the folder where the transmittal package will be created, and then click OK.</cmd>
      </step>
      <step>
        <cmd>In the Modify Transmittal Setup dialog box, click OK to close the dialog
 box.</cmd>
      </step>
      <step>
        <cmd>In the Transmittal Setups dialogbox,
 click Close.</cmd>
      </step>
      <step>
        <cmd>(Optional) Specify any additional comments
 to include with the report
 file from the text
 box for Entering notes to include with this transmittal package in Create Transmittal dialog box.</cmd>
      </step>
      <step>
        <cmd>Click OK to create the transmittal package
 in the folder you specified.</cmd>
      </step>
    </steps>
    <result>
      <p>
        <table>
          <tgroup cols="1" colsep="1" rowsep="1">
            <colspec colname="c1" align="left" />
            <tbody>
              <row>
                <entry colname="c1">
                  <image href="../graphics/ZWCAD_UG_manual_2020_topic776_image001.png" />
                </entry>
              </row>
            </tbody>
          </tgroup>
        </table>
 To create
 transmittal package for self-extracting executable or ZIP file</p>
      <ol>
        <li>Select File &gt; etransmit from the
 mainmenu</li>
        <li>In the Create
 Transmittal dialog box, under Files Tree or Files Table area, click Add File button.</li>
        <li>In the Open folder,
 select the file to be added to the transmittal package, and then click
 Open. The user can optionally repeat this procedure to add more files into transmittalpackage.</li>
        <li>To clear the
 selection of files being added into the transmittal package, click the check box marks beside any files on the Files Tree or Files Table.</li>
        <li>Clickthe Transmittal Setups button,
 select a transmittal setup from the Transmittal<p>Setups dialog box, and then
 click Modify button.</p></li>
        <li>In the Modify Transmittal Setup dialog box, set the transmittal package
 type as ZIP (*.zip) or Self-extracting executable (*.exe).</li>
        <li>Under Transmittal File Folder, click
 Browse to specify the folder where the<p>transmittalpackage to be created.
 A standard file selection dialog box is displayed.</p></li>
        <li>Select the folder where the transmittal package will be created,
 and then click OK.</li>
        <li>In the Modify Transmittal Setup dialog box, click OK to close the dialog
 box.</li>
        <li>In the Transmittal Setups dialogbox,
 click Close.</li>
        <li>(Optional) Specify any additional comments
 to include with the report
 file from the text
 box for Entering notes to include with this transmittal package in Create Transmittal dialog box.</li>
        <li>Click OK to create the transmittal package
 in the folder you specified.</li>
      </ol>
      <p>
        <table>
          <tgroup cols="1" colsep="1" rowsep="1">
            <colspec colname="c1" align="left" />
            <tbody>
              <row>
                <entry colname="c1">
                  <fig>
                    <image href="../graphics/ZWCAD_UG_manual_2020_topic776_image001.png" />
                  </fig>
                </entry>
              </row>
            </tbody>
          </tgroup>
        </table>
 To unpack a self-extracting executable transmittal package</p>
      <ol>
        <li>Double-click the transmittalpackage file in Windows Explorer.</li>
        <li>In Extractor
 dialog box, select Browse to specify the folder where you
 want to unpack the transmittal files.</li>
        <li>Click OK.</li>
        <li>If the transmittal package is password protected,
 system prompt for entering the password.</li>
        <li>Click OK to close each dialog box.</li>
      </ol>
    </result>
  </taskbody>
</task>